In the background, you might
want to make a live stream.
Filters from a beach, a sea with the sea.
This is an athlete for a brand-free,
aiendo,
aida
,ially,
with a boat.
I'm happy to thank you all for
the support of the universe.
Oh, my God.
Chief, no!
Thank you
so
much
for joining us. Let's go!
I'm ready for this burger!
Let's do this
burger!
Hey, I'm made of way.
In the head of the head,
the headzoo doo doo?
Alright!
The head of the head of the
head, take it's a shake?
The queen of the princess!
Let's do it on the 형!
Bam bam bam!
I'm running all the way.
I made it in the head of the head.
I will kill you, I will kill you!
I will kill you, I will kill you?
I can't bear you not coming, Master!
We're 100 % wool.
Would you please check us out, Master?
Bounce on over.
We're a maid cafe.
Hello, Mistress.
Moo, you like to come
and rest for a bit? Wow.
Real maid cafe girls.
Amazing!
They're all so cute!
And there's so many of them!
I can't believe I'm really
here in Akiva! Hello, mistress!
If you bring this flyer in with you, you
won't have to pay the service charge.
Come check us out, meow!
Oh, thank you so much for this!
I definitely want to go! Meow?
This is it.
Welcome to the pigsty, young mistress.
Sorry, Oink, but we're not open.
Oh, no, that's not it.
I'm the new maid starting
here today, Nagomi Wahira.
It's very nice to meet you.
Hey, Chief.
Person here for you.
Oh, it's the new girl. Hi. Yes, it's me.
First thing, can you
go and change, please?
Good morning!
Wow, she's so mature looking.
It's gonna be so nice to
work with such a pretty maid.
Okay, let's see, huh?
I've always dreamed of
wearing a maid outfit.
It's so cute!
Okay, let's do this.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Nagomi Wahira.
I'm here for the live-in
position at the cafe.
I'm 17 years old.
I've always dreamed of being a cute maid
working in a cafe, so I'll do my best.
Your dream is really to be
a maid in this day and age?
You'll manage fine.
The timing doesn't matter at all.
The important thing is that you're young.
What you're feeling right
now, you should treasure that.
I will!
Okay, let's see the other new girl.
Permission to speak, number
96, Runko Menon, 35 years old.
That's funny, you're almost 40.
You're gonna hire a 35-year-old rookie?
Really, Chief? She'll be fine.
Her age shouldn't matter.
People can start over however many
times, as long as they're motivated.
I'm super motivated.
That's awesome. Great.
Okay, then.
Starting today, we'll have to do
our best with the four of you.
Sorry to ask this, but
what's that over there?
Oh, that's our panda, Okachi-machi.
Okachi-a what?
You've never seen a panda?
No, I...
It's cute, isn't it?
Oh right, it's an Akiba
maid cafe after all.
Of course you have to have a panda or two.
Not usually though.
Zitzi act, huh?
Pretty solid newbie.
That's what you're going with?
No, anyway, we're pressed for time,
so I'm gonna open up. Oh, great.
Oh yeah, one more thing.
Don't you two mysteriously
disappear on me too.
I've always wanted to be a maid,
so I'll work really hard as
if my life depends on it.
Wow, this is such a sweet surprise.
Seeing so many handsome
masters sitting here before
me fills a girl like me
up with so much happiness.
Oinky-doink.
I hope I can be like her one day.
You'd have to give up being human then.
She's off on a whole other planet.
This is my personal recommendation.
Give up being human.
Yo, new girls.
Will you serve these oinky-doink
drinks to our masters?
Yes, will do right away, chief.
Super duper smooch. Huh?
Please join me, master.
Oh, okay.
Super duper smooch.
Listen, you've got to
pump things up a notch.
But I was super pumped.
More like...
Oinky smooch, doinky
smooch, oinky doink doink!
You get it?
Oinky smooch doinky smooch oinky
doinky doink are you embarrassed?
No not ever.
Okay i'm going to nail my first task as
a maid i'm going to give up being human.
Just like yumechi oink i'm fresh out of
smoochy ham forest i'm
oinky doink maid nagomi
I love eating widdle-biddy acorns.
My hobby is relaxing and
chatting with my good friend, Mr.
Sparrow.
Okay...
Very half-picked to
make your acquaintance!
Mmm!
Oinky-doink! Hey! Oink?
Let's read the manual properly, shall we?
Thanks for coming.
Let us send you off, Master.
See you later.
Come again. Bye.
I'm sorry about today.
I promise I will try even harder.
So please bear with me.
Just don't make trouble for my
regulars and you'll be okay.
So sorry.
Great.
I finally get to be a maid, and
there's no time to be discouraged.
Welcome home to the pigsty!
Please come in!
Hey, Nagami!
Oh, perhaps this is your
first visit to the maid cafe.
You don't have to be
nervous about it, Master.
Actually, I just started
as a maid today myself.
Here's your oinky-doink water.
Drinking too much will turn you into
a widow piglet, so please be careful.
If you drink too much,
you'll turn into a piglet.
Manager!
Can I see you over here?
Of course. Gladly.
I do believe you're a little behind on
delivering those party favors you owe me.
Huh?
No, no.
Those do's aren't due now.
I'm so very sorry!
Won't you please give us a
little more time, Master?
Do you really not understand your
place in this situation here?
The only reason swine-like
you are in business is
because of your affiliation
with the Creatureland Group.
If you truly understood,
then those words wouldn't be coming
out of your mouth, now would they?
Of course not!
I'm very much aware of that, Master.
Then let me see you pinch out those do's.
No luck.
You can do it!
Not working.
Try squeezing harder.
Sorry, nothing there.
Well, if you can't deliver the
goods, I'll take that mate there!
She can be the one to handle
the wuv wuv moonbeam issue.
He wants me?
No, I can't have her do that.
She literally just joined our pen today.
You sure about that?
You want to squeeze some more?
I can wait.
Hey, Nagomi, I'm going to need you
to do a very important job for us.
Oh, sure.
I'll do anything for the cafe.
Anyways, let's see.
Nagomi, I want you to go deliver
something to the Wuv Wuv Moonbeam.
Wuv Wuv Moonbeam?
It's a maid cafe, one that happens to be
run by our parent company's competitor.
Anyway, I want you to go over
there and hand them this envelope.
An envelope?
Great.
Will you deliver this
for us, please? Sure.
I'll do my best to do a good job.
Man, I'm sorry.
I hate asking you to do this.
I feel so bad.
I'm super sorry. It's fine.
Just leave it to me, Chief.
Can I help you, Ronko?
Please let me accompany
her on this errand.
Huh?
Nah, I don't think you should
tack along on this one.
Please, Chief.
Uh, uh...
Why not?
It'll be a good experience
for the newbies to share.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, fine then.
The two of you can go.
But before you leave, you two should get
yourself something nice to eat first.
The pork broth ramen
downstairs is pretty good.
Are you sure?
Thank you so very much!
Excuse me, one soy milk tofu skin ramen.
Ain't got that.
Ramen, extra veggies, topped with
sauce, fat, and a load of garlic.
Same as ever, huh?
Yumechi's oinky-doink drink is so good.
I really envy her skills.
I guess she has a special
way of infusing it with love.
I want to try harder so I
can be of use to the cafe.
I think it's really amazing
that you're a maid at 35, Ronco.
Thank you for the food.
Duly received you think they'll make it
back safely who cares if they do they
both majorly suck as maids whoa that's
cold dude hey do you two believe in
miracles miracles yeah miracles I can see
it a future where those two are smiling
wallowing around like cute piglets Then
why are you making a new hire flyer?
Really?
Wow, it's so pretty.
Permission to speak, number 96.
I'm Ronko Manon from Oinky Doink Cafe.
I'm Nagomi Wahira.
We're here on an errand.
Let me check and see if
my manager is available.
Just wait here.
Check it out, Ronko.
Apparently their theme
is rabbits on the moon.
So adorable.
Please hop on in and wait right here.
No!
Please spare me!
Just chop it off already!
Are you shitting me?
Straight from the fucking ribs, goddammit!
No!
My pink tail!
My beautiful pink tail!
Oh, no!
I apologize for the wait, Mistresses.
What brings you two hair today?
Well, we're just, uh, here, Mistress.
Read it out loud. Hopké.
Yo, roaches with your stupid antenna.
Prepare to be exterminated from
everyone at Oinky Doink Cafe.
Tell me, what do these
look like to you? Huh?
I'm talking about these
things on our heads.
Like...
like ears?
Bunny ears?
Damn right these are bunny ears!
You got something to say for yourself!
No, ma 'am.
I don't!
Stop snorting, smelly
pig, and speak up! I...
I'm sorry! What's that?
Ah!
Oh, I never took my bib off.
It's stained now, but I guess
that's what paper bibs are for.
This conversation is over. What? Huh?
But we didn't have a conversation.
Let's go.
Oh, okay. Bye.
Dad, you can get there!
Don't let the man alive!
It's our last number, here we go!
It's titled The Pure Maze
Killer Kiss Oinkie Doinkie!
Reach over me and open up the door.
Come in and see what we have in store!
Master, you promised your
eyes were only for me.
Don't you look at no one else!
I will cast a spell on
you, darling, darling.
The purer, the love, it gets dirty, dirty?
Oh, won't you hear for me, I'll to
myself, hey, now won't you please?
You are my cutie pie
heart, boom, kissy kissy,
fruit, fruit Come on to
my never-ending dream,
while I'll make you escape I'll give you
all my love, kill it, kill it, you, you,
you, you Pulling your head to your
temple and all Now is it time,
close your eyes, three,
three, two, one, now go with me
Sending out punches of super-duper smooth
you, you And have a good night now
You are my lovey-dovey
heart So guilty, guilty,
smooth So you'll come to my
never-ending dream I'll miss you,
escape I'll give you all my love Kill it,
kill it, you, you Yeah, you guys,
we are Cuddling with all of my love
Now is the time Close your eyes Three,
two, one You're doing me Sending up
bunches of super-duper smooth chairs
there's no stopping me no sound of
love up in flame meat and purity
auto control you're at my target I'm
gonna shoot you sugar baby love you
please don't shoot me
I'll do anything you ask of me
Allow me to send you off, mistress.
My very first day living
my dream of being a maid.
And I'm ready to leave.
Moe moe kyu
Sore ga tai no ikinza masa
Baka ni suru yatsa Chii o miru ze
Mune o yo miru
Tame nai wa
Itami de oshietokure
Uh, hi.
It's a miracle. Told you!
I totally predicted the future.
Your uniform looks awful.
Yeah, it does.
Nagomi, you need to change.
I moved all of your stuff into your room.
My room?
Fourth floor, at the end.
Oh.
Right.
What was that?
I didn't sign up for this.
I need to get out of here, now!
There are no other rooms,
so for now I'm supposed to be sharing
these living quarters with you.
I look forward to a long relationship.
May we forever work well together.
I can't get away.